Whatever side you're on, see another side.
Mitt is a documentary film directed by Greg Whiteley.
A filmmaker is granted unprecedented access to a political
candidate and his family as he runs for President.
Self, played by Mitt Romney.
Self (archive footage), played by Candy Crowley.
Self, played by Eric Draper.
Self (archive footage), played by Jim Lehrer.
Self (archive footage), played by John McCain.
Self (archive footage), played by Barack Obama.
Mitt is a 2014 American documentary film that chronicles the 2008 and 2012
presidential campaigns of former Massachusetts governor Mitt Romney.
Mitt premiered at the Sundance Film Festival on January 17, 2014.
The film was released on Netflix on January 24, 2014.
The film explores themes of presidential election,
politician, presidential debate.